ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Folder #3 (Laundry Industry) - Fair Labor Standards Act/ Minimum Wage, 1961-1962 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Folder #4 (Laundry Industry) - Wages and Hours, 1954-1967 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Folder #5 (Laundry Industry), 1945 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Folder #6 - (Laundry Industry) - Linen Supply and Flatwork, 1940-1950 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Folder #7 (Laundry Industry) - Piece Rates, 1947-1953 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Folder #8 (Laundry Industry) - Wages and Hours, 1937-1952 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Folder #9 (Laundry Industry), 1946-1950 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Folder #10 (Laundry Industry) - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1948-1950 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Folder #11 - Economic Conditions/Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1948-1949 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Folder #12 (Laundry Industry) - Wages/Industrial Organizations/Unions, 1946-1947 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Folder #13 (Laundry Industry) - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947-1966 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Folder #14 (Laundry Industry), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Folder #15 - Photographs, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Sidney Hillman, 1938-1946 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Folder #17 - Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation ACWA-TWUA (Exhibits A-D), 1976 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Folder #18 - Mergers/Agreements/Letters TWUA, ACWA, ACTWU, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Folder #19 - Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation (TWUA,ACWA-ACTWU), 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Folder #20 - Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation ACWA-TWUA (Exhibits E-M), 1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Folder #21 Respiratory Surveillance Seminars/Anatomy, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Folder #16 - Merger - June. Structure, Coordination of Departments, Services, etc. & Personnel., 1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Folder #16 - ACWA - TWUA Constitutional Comparisons, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Folder #16 - Dues Paying Members TWUA, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Folder #16 - Fact Sheet for a Dues Increase, 1971-1976 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Folder #16 - Jack Rubenstein's Proposal, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Folder #16 - Dues Discussion Excerpt of June 6, TWUA Convention Proceedings on Finance Committee Report, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Folder #16 - Dues & Per Capita Local Payments, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Folder #16 - Income and Expenses Regional Members, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Folder #16 - TWUA/ACTWU Financial Comparison re. Merger, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Folder #16 - Post Merger Staff and Salary Discussions Sol Stetin and Jack Sheinkman, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Information Reported by ACWA Affiliates on the Apparel Plant Information Survey Questionnaires First Quarter, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  Book with sub-tabbed sections
- The Men's Clothing Industry by J.W. Hathcock. March, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  National Recovery Administration Division of Review
- New York State - Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance - Background Materials on ACWA Participation, Summer, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- The Wool Bureau - Graphic Review of the United States Wool Situation, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- The Dress Industry (A Study of the Impact of Fashion on the ways of Business) By: Helen Everett- Part I, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Cotton, Leather, and Allied Garments and Uniform Cut (Including both monthly and annual data - Men's $ Boys'), 1939-1941 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Analysis of Economic Conditions of US Apparel Industry and Present and Prospective Impact of Imports, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- The Cotton Garment Industry by J.W. Hathcock, August., 1935 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Business Prospects for the Mens' and Boys' Clothing Industry, 1957-1960 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- The Financial Experience of the Men's and Boys' Clothing Industry, 1945-1960 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- New Jersey - Economic Data in Support of a Request for a Wage increase in the Cleaning and Dyeing Industry in New Jersey. March 13, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Statements by the Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- The Mechanics of Sewing by Warson M. Hannan, 1953-1963 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Approved ARA Training Projects - Apparel Industry, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- U.S. Bureau of the Census - Facts for Industry; Girls', Children's, and Infants Outerwear, 1946-1952 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Cotton, Leather and Allied Garments & Uniforms Cut (Including both monthly and annual data) (Men's & Boys'), 1930-1932 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Leather, Leather Goods and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Area Redevelopment Administration Loans and Grants to the Apparel Industry, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Minutes of the International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation (General Council, Executive Committee, Subcommittee and Merger Congress), 1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- International Wool Study Group Eighth Session (Vol.III: Official Documents 31-44; Summary Record of Meetings; Bibl. Of end-use Statistics; 7th Session. Misc. Papers), 1962-1964 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- International Wool Study Group Eighth Session (Vol.I; Briefing Book for the United States Delegation), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico Industrial Tax Exemption: Federal Manufacturing Company (i.e. Spencer Manufacturing Company), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Industrial Tax Exemption: Trouser Corporation of Puerto Rico (i.e. A.A. Fogley), 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- International Wool Study Group Eighth Session (Vol.II: Table of Contents to Vols. II and III; Official Documents 1-30), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Arbitration: Statement in Support of Request of the Cleaners and Dryers Union, Local 239 of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America for an Increase in Wages and… New York City. May 23., 1941 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- U.S. Bureau of the Census. Men's and Boys' Apparel Cuttings., 1923-1934 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association of the USA - Miscellaneous Statements and Publications, 1948-1958 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Cuttings of Men's and Boys' Clothing (Project File #12), 1935-1939 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Hours of Work in Relation to Health and Efficiency (NY State Dept. of Labor, Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Men's Wear Annual Business Survey and Men's Wear Fact Book, 1955-1957 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Training Apparel Workers Under the Manpower Development and Training Act of 1962 - ACWA's Position, 1962-1964 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association of the USA - Trends in the Boys' and Students' Clothing Industry, 1954-1958 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Cotton, Leather and Allied Garments and Uniforms Cut (Including both monthly and annual data) (Men's & Boys'), 1933-1938 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Apparel Surveys - U.S. Bureau of the Census. Current Industrial Reports., 1947-1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- ACWA Statements on Foreign Trade (sans Press Releases and Congressional Testimony), 1961 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- ILGWU, TWUA and Other Union Statements on Imports, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Analysis of Economic Conditions of the US Apparel Industry and Present and Prospective Impact of Imports, 1964-1970 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Statements Prepared by Research Dept., 1966 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- ACWA Statements on Foreign Trade - Press Releases, 1959-1963 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Financial Statements of Men's Clothing Manufacturers (Prepared for the 1963 contract negotiations), 1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Statements on Foreign Trade, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- U.S. Bureau of the Census Men's & Boys' Clothing & Cotton and Allied Garments (Fact for industry series), 1942-1947 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Cotton, Leather and Allied Garments and Uniforms Cut (Including both monthly and annual data)(Men's & Boys'), 1923-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- The Hosiery Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee #((99-B)) Pre-Hearing Statements, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Hosiery Industry in Puerto Rico (Committee 111B), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Equal Pay for Equal Work Legislation - Testimony., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Pre-Hearing Statements for the Leather, Leather Goods, and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico (Industry Committee No.100-B) April, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association of the USA - Production Research Report, 1953-1957 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Brief on Behalf of the ACWA and ILGWU with Regard to TSUS Numbers Listed in Annex A, before the Trade Information Committee (January 3), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- U.S. Bureau of the Census - Facts for Industry: Underwear, Knit Cloth and Knit Fabric Gloves (Excluding 1945-1955), 1940-1959 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence (List of Companies) (Box 62, Folder 1)
- ACE Bandage. Inc., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Adele Manufacturing Corporation (Cases refer to Harwood Manufacturing), 1963 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- ADES, Maurice (P.R.), 1958 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Robert Ades (Perfect Shirt, Inc.), 1972 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Aguada Manufacturing. Co., Inc. (Aguada, P.R.), 1967-1970 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Albrey Pants, Inc., 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Alfredo Manufacturing. Corporation (Cases refer to Hardwood Manufacturing) (P.R.), 1957-1969 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Algarin and Briganty, Inc. (P.R.), 1959-1968 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Alonso, Laudelino (Commercial), 1964-1970 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- American Fashion, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Anasco Glove Inc., 1958-1971 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Anasco Sports Co. Inc - ACWA, 1961-1974 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Angus America Corp, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Angus International Corp, 1965-1970 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Angus Manufacturing. Co., Inc. (P.R.), 1956-1961 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Pedro Anibarro Inc., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Arcelay, Maria Luisa (P.R.) (Box 62, Folder 18)
  Empty
- Arecibo Mills, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Martinez Arias & Co., 1965-1968 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Arias Originals, Inc., 1963 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Artex of P.R. Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Aschner Manufacturing. Co. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Attilio Originals International, Inc., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Balcourt Manufacturing., Inc (Affiliate of Fabrini Imports) (Box 62, Folder 25)
- The Baren's Cap Inc., 1962 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Bargaintown of Puerto Rico, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Bargain Town U.S.A. of P.R., 1970 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Baronware Corp, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Barrer, Sidney (P.R.), 1959 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Barry Corp. (P.R.), 1955-1965 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Basewiez Bros, Inc., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Bayco, Inc., 1976 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Beaufab Manufacturing, Inc., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Beauman Manufacturing. Inc., 1967 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Bentley Manufacturing Corporation., 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Bernadot, Inc., (P.R.), 1967 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Best Coat & Apron Manufacturing. Co., Inc., 1965 (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Black Horse Inc. of Puerto Rico, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Ciervo Blanco, Inc., 1967 (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Jose Blanco & Co., 1959-1968 (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Blanco and Riers Santurce, (P.R.), 1964-1968 (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Blanes, Inc., Sucesores de (P.R.), 1956-1962 (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Block Industries of Puerto Rico, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Blue Bell of Lajes, Inc., 1973 (Box 62, Folder 45)
- Blue Bell of Puerto Rico, 1966-1969 (Box 62, Folder 46)
- Blue Star Inc. Mayaguez, P.R., 1959-1971 (Box 62, Folder 47)
- Bobbie Knitwear, Inc., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 48)
- Bonita, Inc., 1962 (Box 62, Folder 49)
  Spanish
- Bonita Uniform Copr., 1959-1967 (Box 62, Folder 50)
- Bonnie Mills, Inc. (P.R.), 1954 (Box 62, Folder 51)
- Boqueron Manufacturing Corp., 1970 (Box 62, Folder 52)
- Borinquen Fashions, Inc., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 53)
- Borinquen Gloves, Inc, 1967-1975 (Box 62, Folder 54)
- Boqueron Manufacturing Corp., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 55)
- Bravada Corp. (Division of the B.V.D. Co. Inc.), 1959-1971 (Box 62, Folder 56)
- Briganty-Principe, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 57)
- Brunswick Corp. (see Brunswick Corp. Chicago, Ill.) (San Juan, P.R.), 1960 (Box 62, Folder 58)
- Brunswick-Royal, Inc., 1960-1971 (Box 62, Folder 59)
- Caguas Accessories, Inc. (P.R.), 1957-1971 (Box 62, Folder 60)
- Caguas Manufacturing Corp., 1958-1968 (Box 62, Folder 61)
- Caguas Mills, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 62, Folder 62)
- Caguas Uniforms Inc. (P.R.), 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 63)
- Calder, Virginia (P.R.) (Box 62, Folder 64)
- Cambridge, Inc., 1960 (Box 62, Folder 65)
- Came Caribe Corporation, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 66)
- Canterbury of P.R. Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 67)
- Capra Corp. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 62, Folder 68)
- Carib Curtain Corp., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 69)
- Carib Co., Inc., - The (See Van Raalte Co., Inc. U.S.) (P.R.), 1959-1961 (Box 62, Folder 70)
- Caribannin Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 62, Folder 71)
- Caribbean Clothing Corp. (P.R.), 1954 (Box 62, Folder 72)
- Caribbean Leisurewear, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 73)
- Caribbean Outerwear Corp. (Yabucoa, Par.), 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 74)
- Caribbean Tanning Co., Inc., 1961 (Box 62, Folder 75)
- Caribe Sports Co. Inc., 1959-1964 (Box 62, Folder 76)
- Caribe Sportswear, Inc., 1959 (Box 62, Folder 77)
- Caribe Underwear Corp., 1965 (Box 62, Folder 78)
- Carlin Manufacturing., Corporation, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 79)
- Carlita Corporation., Hormigueros, P.R., 1966 (Box 62, Folder 80)
- Carmina Busquets (P.R.), 1958 (Box 62, Folder 81)
- Casino Clothing Inc., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 82)
- Castillo, J., F., Inc. (P.R.), 1967 (Box 62, Folder 83)
- Castle Corp. (P.R.) (Box 62, Folder 84)
- Catalan Gonzalez & CIA., Inc., 1972 (Box 62, Folder 85)
- Cee Products, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 86)
- Central American Split Company, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 62, Folder 87)
- Century of Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 88)
- Chadbourn Caribbean Industries., Inc., 1973 (Box 62, Folder 89)
- Central Knitting Mills Inc, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 90)
- Ciales Mfg. Co., 1971-1973 (Box 62, Folder 91)
- Ciales Shirt Company Ciales, (P.R.), 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 92)
- Cielomar Fashions Corp., 1977 (Box 62, Folder 93)
- Cintron, Rose Embroidery Works (P.R.) (Box 62, Folder 94)
- City Club Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 95)
- Loran S. Clark, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 96)
- Clubman of Mayaguez, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 97)
- Coamo Fashions, Inc., 1973 (Box 62, Folder 98)
- Coamo Glove Corporation., 1963-1971 (Box 62, Folder 99)
- Coamo Knitting Mills, Inc., 1963-1967 (Box 62, Folder 100)
- Coamo Spinning Corporation, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 101)
- Tomas Conception Colon, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 102)
- Colonial Corporation of Puerto Rico, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 103)
- Commonwealth Sports Products Inc., 1963 (Box 62, Folder 104)
- Confecciones Oneida, Inc., 1976 (Box 62, Folder 105)
- Conro Manufacturing Co., Cabo Rojo, Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 106)
- Consolidated Knitting Mills Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 62, Folder 107)
- Continental Pants Inc., 1964 (Box 62, Folder 108)
- Coqui de San Lorenco, Inc., 1976 (Box 62, Folder 109)
- Coral Clothing Corp. Mayaguez, (P.R.), 1960-1965 (Box 62, Folder 110)
- Corozal Knitting Mills, Inc. (P.R.), 1958-1973 (Box 62, Folder 111)
- Corlita Corp., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 112)
- Cortefiel. Inc, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 113)
- Henry P. Cowen (P.R.), 1960 (Box 62, Folder 114)
- Creaciones Greisa, Inc., 1975 (Box 62, Folder 115)
- Crescendoe Glove Co. (See Anasco Gloves Inc., Puerto Rico) (U.S.), 1960-1962 (Box 62, Folder 116)
- Crobar Uniforms Manufacturing Co., 1971 (Box 62, Folder 117)
- Aldo Croatti, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 118)
- Cubanita, Inc. La (P.R.), 1954-1955 (Box 62, Folder 119)
- Damas Pajama Corp., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 120)
- Davis of Puerto Rico, Inc., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 121)
- Sucesores de Blanes inc., 1932-1968 (Box 62, Folder 122)
- DeRogatis of P.R., Inc., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 123)
- Diaz Needlework Co. (P.R.) (Box 62, Folder 124)
- Diaz Soto, Praxedes, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 125)
- Disposable Safety Wear, Inc., 1977 (Box 62, Folder 126)
- Domenech, Gloria, E. (P.R.), 1954-1970 (Box 62, Folder 127)
- Dorado Leather Manufacturing. Corp., 1962 (Box 62, Folder 128)
- Dorado Manufacturing Corp. (P.R.), 1959 (Box 62, Folder 129)
- Durawear Manufacturing Corp., 1962-1967 (Box 62, Folder 130)
- E.J. Sportswear Inc., 1963 (Box 62, Folder 131)
- Eastfield Knitting Mills, Inc.- San German, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 132)
- Edro & Anasco Anasco (P.R.), 1967 (Box 62, Folder 133)
- Edro Corporation, 1953-1970 (Box 62, Folder 134)
- Elaine Garments, Inc. (Formerly Continental Pants Co. Mayaguez, P.R.), 1959-1962 (Box 62, Folder 135)
- El Finale, Inc., 1961-1971 (Box 62, Folder 136)
- Eleven Eleven Corporation, 1962-1971 (Box 62, Folder 137)
- El Rey Pajama Corp., (P.R.), 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 138)
- Wiston Ely, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 139)
- Empire Textile Corp., (Corozal, P.R.), 1967-1974 (Box 62, Folder 140)
- EPNG Corp., (P.R.), 1967 (Box 62, Folder 141)
- Esquire Manufacturing. Corp. (P.R.), 1955-1971 (Box 62, Folder 142)
- Esteva Puerto Rico, Inc. (Hatillo, P.R.), 1960 (Box 62, Folder 143)
- W. Estrada Co. Inc. (Wilfredo Estrada), 1976 (Box 62, Folder 144)
- European Knitting Industries, Inc., 1967 (Box 62, Folder 145)
- Lawrence Evin, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 146)
- Exotic Leather Corp., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 147)
- Exquisite Form Industries, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 62, Folder 148)
- Fabrikato, Inc., 1974 (Box 62, Folder 149)
- Fabrini Imports, Ltd., 1962 (Box 62, Folder 150)
- Fajardo Apparel (Puerto Rico), 1967 (Box 62, Folder 151)
- Fajardo Knitting Mills, Inc. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 62, Folder 152)
- Fale Tanning Co., Inc. (Dorado, P.R.), 1962 (Box 62, Folder 153)
- Family Garment, Inc., 1961 (Box 62, Folder 154)
- Feliana Inc., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 155)
- Almacenes Ferrer, Inc., 1969 (Box 62, Folder 156)
- Fibers International Corporation, 1968-1971 (Box 62, Folder 157)
- Finetex Hosiery Co. Inc. (Sub. Of Kaiser Roth Corp N.Y.), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 158)
- Formacraft Equipment Company, Inc., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 159)
- Four Star Industries, Inc. Penneias, P.R., 1965-1970 (Box 62, Folder 160)
- Sol Friedman, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 161)
- Angel David Gonzalez Fuentes, 1966-1969 (Box 62, Folder 162)
- G.F. Mills, Inc, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- G.M. Gloves Corp., (P.R.), 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Nat Galston, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Gamma Creations (P.R.) (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Garcia & Annoni, Inc., 1961 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Frederick Theodor Gaspard (San Juan, P.R.), 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Gem Gloves, Inc., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Gemsco Manufacturing. Co. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- General Mills Textiles, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- General Needlecraft Co. (P.R.) (Box 63, Folder 10)
- General Nitewear of Puerto Rico, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Julio E. Geraldino., Barinas Ward, Yauco. Puerto Rico., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Gerchen, Bernard (P.R.), 1958 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Glamourette Fashion Mills, Inc., 1976 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Gloresto, Inc., 1971 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Gloria Lingerie, Inc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Glosamar Mills, Inc., 1971 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Gold Manufacturing Corporation, 1959-1962 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Goldsmith Co. of Puerto Rico, Inc., (See Gant Madeleine Inc. U.S.) (P.R.), 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Gomez, Elias Blanco (P.R.), 1957 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Catalan Gonzales & Co., Santurce, PR, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Gonzalez & Co., Inc (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Industrial Gonzalez Inc., 1968 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Gonzalez, Luis Acevedo (P.R.), 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Gorbea, Perez, Morell, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Grajales, Jose R. (P.R.), 1952 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Grana Underwear Corporation., Puerto Rico, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Guantes de Ponce, Inc., 1964-1970 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Stuart H. Green, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Guayama Children's Wear Co. Inc., (Guayama, P.R.), 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Guaynabo Handcraft Corp. (Guaynabo, P.R.), 1976 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Gumdrops, Puerto Rico, Inc., 1968 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- M. Gutierrez & CIA., Inc. 113 Antonie R. Barcelo St. Arecibo, P.R., 1958 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Guzman Tiburcio, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 34)
- Haddon Corp., 1958 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Harem Fashions of P.R., Inc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 36)
- Harwood Manufacturing (Alfredo Mfg. Corp., Rio Grande Mfg. Corp., Adele Mfg. Corp., Rio Monte Mfg. Corp.), 1967-1969 (Box 63, Folder 37)
- hatillo Apparel Corp; Hatillo, Puerto Rico, 1961-1971 (Box 63, Folder 38)
- Hatillo Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 39)
- Health-Tex Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 40)
- Hemming, C.,& G., Inc. (P.R.), 1967 (Box 63, Folder 41)
- Hero Manufacturing Corporation., 1977 (Box 63, Folder 42)
- M.S. Hoffman, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 43)
- Hosetex Corp. (Sub. of Kaiser Roth Corp., N.Y.), 1969 (Box 63, Folder 44)
- House of Nash, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 45)
- Hunnicutt Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 63, Folder 46)
- Industrias Aguila, Inc. (Eagle Work Clothes, Inc.) Irvington, N.J.), 1973 (Box 63, Folder 47)
- Infants and Toddlers, Inc., 1976 (Box 63, Folder 48)
- Isla Pajama Corp. (P.R.), 1966-1971 (Box 63, Folder 49)
- Island Uniforms, Inc., 1976 (Box 63, Folder 50)
- Inter Malla Corporation., 1970 (Box 63, Folder 51)
- Intermaya Olympic Corporation., 1971 (Box 63, Folder 52)
- J.P.T. Fashions, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 53)
- JRN Manufacturing Corporation., 1968-1972 (Box 63, Folder 54)
- Joal Manufacturing Corporation., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 55)
- Janrico, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 56)
- Evelyn Judith Products, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 57)
- Juncos Sport Company, Inc., 1959-1971 (Box 63, Folder 58)
- Kaufman, Alfred S. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 63, Folder 59)
- Kayser-Roth Hosiery Corp de Puerto Rico, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 60)
- Keith of P.R., Inc., 1969 (Box 63, Folder 61)
- Keller Glove Manufacturing. Co. (P.R.), 1952 (Box 63, Folder 62)
- Kelly Park, Ltd., 1977 (Box 63, Folder 63)
- Kenny Manufacturing Corp., 1960 (Box 63, Folder 64)
- Keyette Manufacturing Corp. (Key Apparel Corp.), 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 65)
- Keyette Manufacturing Corporation, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 66)
- Rudy Kiesler, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 67)
- Kit Manufacturing Corp., 1966 (Box 63, Folder 68)
- Klad Corporation, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 69)
- Knitco, Inc., Toca Alte, P.R., 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 70)
- Knitcraft Products, Inc., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 71)
- Kraytex Undergarment Corporation (NY), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 72)
- La Cubanita, Inc., 1955 (Box 63, Folder 73)
- Las Palmas Manufacturing. Co. Inc., 1964 (Box 63, Folder 74)
- La Torre Co., Inc. (P.R), 1962 (Box 63, Folder 75)
- Ladies Fashions Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 63, Folder 76)
- Harry Lang Manufacturing Company of P.R., Inc (also Haddon Corporation), 1959 (Box 63, Folder 77)
- Lares Mills, Inc., 1963-1972 (Box 63, Folder 78)
- Las Palmas Manufacturing. Co., Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 79)
- Laudelino Alonso Y CIA, Inc., 1958 (Box 63, Folder 80)
- Laudelino Alonso & Co. Jundos, P.R., 1964-1973 (Box 63, Folder 81)
- Law-Ray Corporation, 1963-1967 (Box 63, Folder 82)
- La Vega Company Inc., 1965 (Box 63, Folder 83)
- Frederick Lee, Inc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 84)
- Lermaj Manufacturing Inc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 85)
- Life Manufacturing Corporation., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 86)
- Lilly-Ann Originals, Inc., 1972 (Box 63, Folder 87)
- Linda Uniforms Cidra, (P.R.), 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 88)
- Lita Inc. (P.R.), 1957 (Box 63, Folder 89)
- Live-ins of P.R., Inc., 1975 (Box 63, Folder 90)
- Lopez, A. & Co. (P.R.), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 91)
- Lord Mike Sportswear, Inc. (P.R.), 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 92)
- Joseph E. Ludden, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 93)
- Jose A. Lugo, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 94)
- Lugo, Ramonita (P.R.), 1958 (Box 63, Folder 95)
- Lumica, Inc., 1968 (Box 63, Folder 96)
- Harold D. Lurie., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 97)
- Ginny Lynn Mills, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 63, Folder 98)